Aurora Teagarden Mysteries: A Very Foul Play is a mystery, tv
movie, thriller film directed by Martin Wood.
At a gathering of mystery and true crime fans, Aurora Teagarden’s nephew, Phillip, is accused of murder when an unplanned onstage blackout during
the play in which he is performing ends, revealing Phillip holding the bloody knife that has just killed one of the other performers.
12th installment in Aurora Teagarden Mysteries
Aurora Teagarden, played by Candace Cameron Bure.
Nick Miller, played by Niall Matter.
Aida Teagarden, played by Marilu Henner.
Sally Allison, played by Lexa Doig.
Det. Arthur Smith, played by Peter Benson.
Lynn Smith, played by Miranda Frigon.
Aurora Teagarden is a fictional character created by author Charlaine Harris.
She is the protagonist of a series of eleven crime
novels written from 1990 to 2017.
Hallmark Movies & Mysteries began  adapting the novels in 2014 for their original film series The Aurora Teagarden
Mysteries with Candace Cameron Bure in the title role, part of the network’s "Mystery Wheel" umbrella series.
In the first book of the series, twenty-eight-year-old Aurora (Roe) Teagarden is a professional librarian at the Lawrenceton Public Library and belongs to
the Real Murders Club, a group of true crime enthusiasts who gather monthly to study famous crimes from the history of their Georgia town.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.